<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[From This Angle]]></title>
  <link href="http://nathanscott.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://nathanscott.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-05-02T23:08:22+10:00</updated>
  <id>http://nathanscott.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Nathan]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything that can be invented has been invented]]></title>
    <link href="http://nathanscott.github.com/blog/2012/05/01/everything-that-can-be-invented-has-been-invented/"/>
    <updated>2012-05-01T12:54:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>http://nathanscott.github.com/blog/2012/05/01/everything-that-can-be-invented-has-been-invented</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  Everything that can be invented has been invented.<br />
  <small>Charles H. Duell, Commissioner, U.S. patent office, 1899 (attributed)</small>
</blockquote>


<p>There were some popular theories that innovation was grinding to a halt as we were essentially &#8220;running out&#8221; areas to innovate.  In fact, the exact opposite is true.  The more innovation that happens, the more areas for further innovation are generated.  <a href="http://www.uspto.gov/web/offices/ac/ido/oeip/taf/cbcby.htm">Patent applications steadily increase</a> year after year.  The most <a href="http://www.fastcompany.com/most-innovative-companies/2012/full-list">innovative companies are also some of the newest</a>.</p>

<p>The concept of &#8216;basic problems&#8217; changes every day the more sophisticated we get as a society.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rome2Rio - New CEO]]></title>
    <link href="http://nathanscott.github.com/blog/2012/03/29/rome2rio-new-ceo/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-29T16:16:00+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://nathanscott.github.com/blog/2012/03/29/rome2rio-new-ceo</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today I met <a href="http://twitter.com/rodcu">Rod Cuthbert</a>, Rome2Rio&#8217;s new CEO. I also learnt the Melbourne startup is frightfully close to closing a round of funding.</p>

<p>Rome2Rio are an end-to-end multi-mode travel search engine helping travellers map routes to and from virtually anywhere in the world.</p>

<p>This round of funding will help secure the next development rollout.</p>

<p>They&#8217;re also moving into new markets. The team is in dealings with <a href="http://www.ubmaviation.com">UMB aviation</a>, who are expected to use Rome2Rio&#8217;s API an capitalist on their extensive data set to provide corporate users smarter alternatives to travel. For example, business meetings between European countries often don&#8217;t require flight travel. Buses, trains and trams offer the most time sensitive and cost effect measures for travel between cities such as Berlin and Paris. Rome2Rio not only has the data to map these routes, but also includes comparison charts to give business folk the flexibility they require. And all via a simple API interface.</p>

<p>Business partner deals may be a significant focus and key differentiator for Rome2Rio as they continue to make their mark as the most effective end to end travel site around.</p>

<p><a href="http://rome2rio.com.au">Rome2Rio.com.au</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, blog already]]></title>
    <link href="http://nathanscott.github.com/blog/2012/03/15/communcation-is-key/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-15T00:30:00+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://nathanscott.github.com/blog/2012/03/15/communcation-is-key</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m not very good at blogging.
But I&#8217;m going to work to get better.</p>

<p>To start with my posts will be quite short.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
